triggit.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Triggit

Opt-Out of Triggit Technology

At Triggit we care about the privacy of Internet Users. We have created this Privacy Policy in order demonstrate this commitment to privacy.

This Privacy Policy represents Triggit's privacy practices across both triggit.com and also for our data use and collection through our advertising services (“Services”). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason, at our sole discretion. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. By using or accessing the Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, and you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us.

Triggit works hard to make sure we stay in compliance with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information. We are a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and adhere to the NAI Code. Through the NAI, Triggit works with industry-leading companies to address important privacy and consumer protection issues in online advertising.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or the Triggit technology, please don't hesitate to contact us at privacy@triggit.com

## Information collected via Triggit.com

Triggit does not collect what is generally called Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) such as your name, email address, postal mailing address, home/mobile telephone number, credit card number and billing information unless you have explicitly provided it via our web forms, email, or phone. If you choose to provide us with PII under these mechanisms, this PII will be stored for a reasonable amount of time.

Triggit does collect non-personally identifiable information (“non-PII”) via Triggit.com. Non-PII includes (but is not limited to) session data, browser information, operating system type, IP address, geographic data, and other generic Internet usage related data. This data is used for Triggit.com site analytics.

## Information collected via Triggit Technology

The Triggit technology works to make digital advertisements more relevant to consumers. To accomplish this, Triggit collects information about the website(s) you visit on behalf of our advertising clients. This information helps makes advertisements served through Triggit more relevant.

The information collected does not include personally identifiable information about you (PII). PII includes things such as your name, address, phone number, social security number or email address. Triggit does collect non-PII about you for the use of targeting ads and measuring the effectiveness of these ads on behalf or our clients. Non-PII data includes: IP address, browser type, operating system, visits to partner websites, clickstream data (including when a Triggit ad was viewed, clicked on, engaged with). This data may result in targeted advertising.

Triggit works hard not to collect data, nor create data segments around sensitive information such as financial information or medical conditions. We may however create highly targeted segments and advertisements; such as putting previously searched flight dates or destinations directly into an ad alongside information or deals on hotel or car rentals. Triggit works to be transparent about how we create segments so that users can make informed decisions about how our technology functions.

Triggit typically records and stores data on users that have visited Triggit.com or a client or a partner site within the last 30 days. If you have not visited triggit.com, a partner or client site, your data will be purged from the system. The maximum amount of time Triggit retain user level data is 12 months from the previous encounter.

## Cookies

Triggit uses form elements and/or cookies to collect information and enable our technology solutions.

A cookie is a short line of text that is attached to your browser when you visit a website or view a particular advertisement. This cookie can then be identified to determine how often you have visited a site or seen particular ad. Cookies are otherwise generic, and cannot be used to access any other information on your computer.

Triggit uses cookie data we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features, information and services outlined at Triggit.com and in conjunction with our advertising technology. Triggit may also use this information to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our users, to improve the way the site and Triggit technology works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.

## Clear GIF's

Clear GIF's are small images on a Web page or other document. These gifs allow the operator of the Web page or other document, or a third party who serves the gif, to set, read, and modify cookies.

## Opting Out

Triggit offer visitors a means for controlling the use of session information with respect to Triggit and our advertising technologies.

The most simple way to opt out of the Triggit cookie (or any other cookie) is through your Internet Browser. In your preferences you can set the browser on your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to features on our Site or other websites which depend upon cookies.

You can also opt-out of Triggit.com by clicking on our opt-out link listed below. This will set a cookie that specifically tells Triggit that you are not interested in our services. If you clear the cookies on your browser, or use a different browser or computer, you must complete the opt-out procedure again.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location.

Triggit complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information.

## Children Under 13 Years of Age

Triggit's advertising products and the Service are not intended for persons under 13 years of age, and are not intentionally developed for or directed to children. We do not knowingly solicit or collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly market our products or services to children under the age of 13.

## Disclosures

Some of our web site partners may place their own cookies on your Internet browser outside of our service; however, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Please be aware that the web sites of our customers as well as the web sites linked through the ads delivered as a result of the Services may collect information from you. Such information may include non-PII through the use of cookies and other technology and any PII you may choose to give in registering and transacting with such web sites. Although we choose our business partners and clients carefully, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of such web sites you visit to determine how they handle any information they collect from you.

Unless you otherwise permit Triggit to share the non-personally identifiable information it has collected about you, we will only share that information with the following third parties and in the following circumstances: (i) to the appropriate authorities when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, or in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person; (ii) to a court of law, arbitration panel, or similar body to enforce or protect our rights either under law or as granted by an agreement; (iii) to any company or entity that acquires all or substantially all of Triggit's assets; or (iv) to third parties that help us provide the Service to Clients (including but not limited to data storage and processing facilities), or that enter into strategic partnerships with Triggit which allow us to expand the Service for our Clients.

We may also share, in an aggregated format, the non-PII we collect to do business with related third parties, such as our advertising clients.

## Opt-Out

## Contact Information

Triggit Inc, 1535 Mission Street, San Francisco, CA 94103

privacy@triggit.com
